# WONG EE KIN

A Business Operations Analyst with hands-on experience in project management in the data labeling industry. Currently servicing and managing Supahand's key enterprise clients. Also the training lead of Supahand's arsenal of data annotators. Strong communicator with the ability to work independently as well as a part of team.

+60 163846949

LinkedIn Profile

# WORK EXPERIENCE -

#### Nov 2021 - Present

## Business Operations Analyst, Supahands Dotcom Sdn Bhd

- Spearheading Supahands' training initiatives for data labelers through a series of educational modules and mentorship approach, to upskill and develop self-aware data labelers.
- Project management and consulting towards clients with data labeling needs, within the Robotics, Agricultural, E-Commerce and Retail industries.
- · Acting as a focal point in a cross-functional team by aligning different departments' expectations and leveraging their resources in order to effectively manage the pipeline of projects.
- · Advocating for clients' business goals, anticipating how to meet those goals, and aligning expectations on how these goals will change over time.
- Provide assistance to the Product team through conducting user-interviews and creating content to obtain feedback for the continuous iteration of Supahands' key products.

## July 2020 - Aug 2020

## Business Consulting Intern, EY

- Providing administrative assistance towards clients and internal stakeholders.
- Initiated regular contact with clients and updated them with project progresses

## June 2019 - Aug 2019

#### Economic Research Intern, Khazanah Research Institute

- Recognized for leading a 3-member intern team in the translation of research content.
- Successfully ironed out any technical issues on research reports before submission.
- Co-authored 1 ground-breaking research article concerning plastic waste in Malaysia.

## EDUCATION -

#### August 2022 - Present

## Sigma School (Part Time)

- Currently learning to code with Sigma School, the colearning coding school that emphasizes on collaborative learning and real world projects to become a job-ready developer upon graduation.
- Student Jumpstarter for August 22' Batch.

## September 2018 - July 2021

#### BSc (Hons) Economics, The University of Nottingham Malaysia

- Classification: First-Class with Honors
- Outstanding Achievement in Year Three Prize Recipient
- High Achievers Scholarship 2018 Recipient

# – SKILLS –

- Google Suite Applications
- Team Collaboration
- Project Management
- Client Retention
- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript

# LANGUAGES

- English
- Mandarin
- Malay